<!-- Here we define the Eco item that will be used for our page's icon in the Ecopedia navigation bar -->
<ecopedia icon="PaperItem">
  <summary>Welcome to the Aurora Eco Server!</summary>

  <!-- The banner section type allows for the addition of images that were previously created inside the client AssetBundle project. 
    These images will attempt to fill the full width of the Ecoepdia page so it is advised to use rectangle images that are longer then they are tall. -->
<!--  <section type="banner" image="EcoLogoSampleImage" /> -->

  <!-- In most cases your page content should be enclosed in the base section tag. This allows the page parser to properly lay out the content
    you give it -->
  <section>
<b>General Server Rules

1. Be Respectful!

2. Stealing from property of others is not allowed. For unclaimed areas it is still advised to follow this rule however this does fall back on the owner of the property.

3. Hostile Takeover of the property of somebody who is not abandoned (at least 0 hours playtime in the last 7 Days) is NOT allowed.

4. All Structures must be supported, no floating or unrealistic builds held up with just a set of stairs.


Season 2 : Skills & Economy

--Skills--
This Season you will only have 3 stars max for profession choices, We encourage NOT taking jobs necessarily in a line like Gather > Farmer > Miller, 
Instead we would rather you choose something like Gather > Farmer, then jump to something else you are interested in that doesn't take supplies from farming. 
By doing this it will allow for better economics on the server and will incentivize better trade. Do feel free to save stars for jobs that come later in gameplay!

An additional note, skills will take longer to level up this season, so expect to not reach level 6 in your skills on the first day you get them.

--Economy--
When setting prices of items to sell, set profit margins higher on less sold items (general baseline profit is 20%), 
stuff that sells far less should have higher margin than something that sells thousands. (examples - flaxseeds = profit of 20%, cars/boats = profit of 60%) 

When setting buy prices, set them a few cents higher than the sell prices of that item (more money the less of the item you are buying).
This will get you the things you need quicker while also stimulating the economy through trade and allowing for individuals to do transport services as a profession
making the difference as profit and a way to pay their expenses.
</b>

We hope you enjoy your stay!


If you would like to stay up to date on our changes be sure to join our Discord!
You can also type the following into chat on Eco to link your account to discord (Be sure to join the discord first): /dl linkaccount "Your Discord Username"
  </section>
  <!-- The button section type creates a clickable button that will open an external URL when clicked. Note: if the URL is not a domain
    that Strange Loop Games has verified as trusted a warning dialog will be presented to the user instead of the normal "open website" dialog box -->
  <section type="button" url="https://discord.gg/z6xbjQqQQr">Click here to join!</section>
</ecopedia>